(Raj:)I'm melt-in-your-mouth caramel.
(Howard:)Oh, man.
(Howard:)Look at my nose.
(Leonard:)Maybe it's a shipping problem.
- What?
- Yeah.
(Leonard:)Maybe Wesley Snipes and Toucan Sam
just got action figures and look like you. Heh.
- This sucks.
- I can't believe I wasted all that money.
(Leonard:)Aw, and my girlfriend
wouldn't let me get one.
(Leonard:)Look at my face.
(Leonard:)Do I look smug? I feel smug.
(Penny:)I hate it when you make me sit
through the credits.
(Leonard:)Well, sometimes there's a secret ending,
like in The Avengers.
Yeah, but I don't think that's gonna
happen in a documentary about the Holocaust.
(Leonard:)They could show bloopers.
(Leonard:)- Oh, no.
- What is that?
That is Sheldon's "I'm unhappy
and about to destroy the planet" music.